Date Ordered: 2018/03/23 18:44:17 +0000
Job: j293422
Name: OpenStreetMap Planet
Data Listing Token: e0dd1ef6-df94-4e7f-a95f-f48327ba3467
Job Token: 296ef69e-0fd0-4100-aac6-11f55453897a


### Contents of Data Order ###

# Data #
The Data folder contains the data that was ordered. The file extension depends on the type of data requested.

# Misc #
The Misc folder contains any additional information the provider included with the dataset. If the provider did not include any additional information, this folder will be empty.

# Description #
The Description File is a copy of the dataset's description as seen on the data listing when the data was ordered.

# Read Me #
The file you are currently reading.

# License #
The License agreement associated with the downloaded data. The license agreement contains information on use restrictions, liability, and disclaimers.